<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on Avisha Kumar</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4321/publications/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on Avisha Kumar</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4321/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A novel open-source ultrasound dataset with deep learning benchmarks for spinal cord injury localization and anatomical segmentation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/publications/arxiv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/publications/arxiv/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: While deep learning has catalyzed breakthroughs across numerous domains, its broader adoption in clinical settings is inhibited by the costly and time-intensive nature of data acquisition and annotation. To further facilitate medical machine learning, we present an ultrasound dataset of 10,223 Brightness-mode (B-mode) images consisting of sagittal slices of porcine spinal cords (N=25) before and after a contusion injury. We additionally benchmark the performance metrics of several state-of-the-art object detection algorithms to localize the site of injury and semantic segmentation models to label the anatomy for comparison and creation of task-specific architectures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visualizing Tactile Feedback: An Overview of Current Technologies With a Focus on Ultrasound Elastography</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/publications/front-med-tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/publications/front-med-tech/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: Tissue elasticity remains an essential biomarker of health and is indicative of irregularities such as tumors or infection. The timely detection of such abnormalities is crucial for the prevention of disease progression and complications that arise from late-stage illnesses. However, at both the bedside and the operating table, there is a distinct lack of tactile feedback for deep-seated tissue. As surgical techniques advance toward remote or minimally invasive options to reduce infection risk and hasten healing time, surgeons lose the ability to manually palpate tissue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unidirectional brain-computer interface: Artificial neural network encoding natural images to fMRI response in the visual cortex.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/publications/ieee-icassp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/publications/ieee-icassp/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: While significant advancements in artificial intelligence (AI) have catalyzed progress across various domains, its full potential in understanding visual perception remains underexplored. We propose an artificial neural network dubbed VISION, an acronym for “Visual Interface System for Imaging Output of Neural activity,” to mimic the human brain and show how it can foster neuroscientific inquiries. Using visual and contextual inputs, this multimodal model predicts the brain’s functional magnetic resonance imaging (fMRI) scan response to natural images.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying tethered spinal cord tension: Ultrasound elastography results from computational, cadaveric, and intraoperative first-in-human studies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/publications/nat-com-med/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/publications/nat-com-med/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: Background: Tension in the spinal cord is a trademark of tethered cord syndrome. Unfortunately, existing tests cannot quantify tension across the bulk of the cord, making the diagnostic evaluation of stretch ambiguous. A potential non-destructive metric for spinal cord tension is ultrasound-derived shear wave velocity (SWV). The velocity is sensitive to tissue elasticity and boundary conditions including strain. We use the term Ultrasound Tensography to describe the acoustic evaluation of tension with SWV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Patient-specific Preplanning Treatment Algorithm for Focused Ultrasound Therapy of Spinal Cord Injury</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/publications/ieee-ner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/publications/ieee-ner/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: Focused ultrasound (FUS) is an increasingly prevalent therapeutic tool used in medicine to treat patients non-invasively, cost-effectively, and without any ionizing radiation. Depending on the clinical application, therapeutic ultrasound can be used for tissue ablation, physiotherapy, lithotripsy, and drug delivery, among other therapies. For the treatment to be effective, it is important to understand the acoustic pressure profile in the tissue to ensure the focal point intensity is sufficient to achieve therapy without damaging the tissue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computational modeling towards focused ultrasound therapy for spinal cord injury: visualization of beam propagation through patient-specific anatomy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/publications/spie-med-imaging/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/publications/spie-med-imaging/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: Ultrasound holds promise for use in spinal cord injury cases for both diagnostic and therapeutic purposes. Focused ultrasound applications demand an added threshold of study to ensure the safety and efficacy of the therapy. For optimal treatment outcomes, it is crucial to understand whether relevant structures are being targeting with sufficient energy without damaging neighboring tissue and vasculature. However, it is difficult to predict the expected displacement and pressure profile of the ultrasound wavefront due to challenges with visualizing an acoustic beam in real-time and complex patient-specific anatomy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulated driving in the epilepsy monitoring unit: Effects of seizure type, consciousness, and motor impairment</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/publications/epilepsia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/publications/epilepsia/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: People with epilepsy face serious driving restrictions, determined using retrospective studies. To relate seizure characteristics to driving impairment, we aimed to study driving behavior during seizures with a simulator. Patients in the Yale New Haven Hospital undergoing video-electroencephalographic monitoring used a laptop-based driving simulator during ictal events. Driving function was evaluated by video review and analyzed in relation to seizure type, impairment of consciousness/responsiveness, or motor impairment during seizures. Fifty-one seizures in 30 patients were studied.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Design of the Alpha CubeSat: Technology Demonstration of a ChipSat-Equipped Retroreflective Light Sail</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/publications/aiaa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/publications/aiaa/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: This paper provides an overview of Alpha, a rapidly developed, low-cost CubeSat mission to verify the performance of a highly retroreflective material for light-sail propulsion. Designed, integrated, and tested by students of the Space Systems Design Studio at Cornell University, this mission demonstrates a number of key technologies that enable next-generation capabilities for space exploration. In particular, this paper focuses on the novel application of ChipSats (gram scale spacecraft-on-a-chip technology) as a means of verifying Alpha&amp;rsquo;s sail orbit and attitude dynamics.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
