<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on Avisha Kumar</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4321/publications/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on Avisha Kumar</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4321/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A novel open-source ultrasound dataset with deep learning benchmarks for spinal cord injury localization and anatomical segmentation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/publications/arxiv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/publications/arxiv/</guid>
      <description>Published in: ArXiv</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visualizing Tactile Feedback: An Overview of Current Technologies With a Focus on Ultrasound Elastography</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/publications/front-med-tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/publications/front-med-tech/</guid>
      <description>Published in: Frontiers in Medical Technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unidirectional brain-computer interface: Artificial neural network encoding natural images to fMRI response in the visual cortex.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/publications/ieee-icassp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/publications/ieee-icassp/</guid>
      <description>Published in: IEEE International Conference on Acoustics, Speech, and Signal Processing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying tethered spinal cord tension: Ultrasound elastography results from computational, cadaveric, and intraoperative first-in-human studies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/publications/nat-com-med/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/publications/nat-com-med/</guid>
      <description>Published in: Nature Communications Medicine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Patient-specific Preplanning Treatment Algorithm for Focused Ultrasound Therapy of Spinal Cord Injury</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/publications/ieee-ner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/publications/ieee-ner/</guid>
      <description>Published in: IEEE Neuroengineering 2023</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computational modeling towards focused ultrasound therapy for spinal cord injury: visualization of beam propagation through patient-specific anatomy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/publications/spie-med-imaging/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/publications/spie-med-imaging/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: Ultrasound holds promise for use in spinal cord injury cases for both diagnostic and therapeutic purposes. Focused ultrasound applications demand an added threshold of study to ensure the safety and efficacy of the therapy. For optimal treatment outcomes, it is crucial to understand whether relevant structures are being targeting with sufficient energy without damaging neighboring tissue and vasculature. However, it is difficult to predict the expected displacement and pressure profile of the ultrasound wavefront due to challenges with visualizing an acoustic beam in real-time and complex patient-specific anatomy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulated driving in the epilepsy monitoring unit: Effects of seizure type, consciousness, and motor impairment</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/publications/epilepsia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/publications/epilepsia/</guid>
      <description>Published in: Epilepsia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Design of the Alpha CubeSat: Technology Demonstration of a ChipSat-Equipped Retroreflective Light Sail</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/publications/aiaa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/publications/aiaa/</guid>
      <description>Published in: American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics SciTech Forum</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
