<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Avisha Kumar</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4321/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Avisha Kumar</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4321/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Netlify</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/collection/day02/01-netlify/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/collection/day02/01-netlify/</guid>
      <description>So far, we&amp;rsquo;ve been leveraging GitHub Pages for publishing. This works great, but for blogdown we&amp;rsquo;ll start using Netlify. Let&amp;rsquo;s start RIGHT NOW with a site we&amp;rsquo;ve already built and published.&#xA;Pre-requisites Pick either your postcards site, or your distill site from day 01. Refresh your memory- which repository was it again?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A GitHub profile</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/collection/day01/01-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/collection/day01/01-github/</guid>
      <description>Profile https://docs.github.com/en/github/setting-up-and-managing-your-github-profile/personalizing-your-profile&#xA;Pin projects to profile https://docs.github.com/en/github/setting-up-and-managing-your-github-profile/pinning-items-to-your-profile&#xA;Profile README This is new! Let&amp;rsquo;s do it:&#xA;https://docs.github.com/en/github/setting-up-and-managing-your-github-profile/managing-your-profile-readme</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prework</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/collection/prework/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/collection/prework/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Introducing Yourself Online workshop! We look forward to meeting you. Before attending the workshop, please complete the following prework.&#xA;Set up RStudio Cloud Sign up for a free RStudio Cloud account at https://rstudio.cloud/ before the workshop. I recommend logging in with an existing Google or GitHub account, if you have one (rather than creating a new account with another password you have to remember). I want you to be able to work from your own laptop in this workshop, but Cloud is an important back-up plan should you run into troubles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A postcard</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/collection/day01/02-postcards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/collection/day01/02-postcards/</guid>
      <description>Pre-requisites First, make sure you have the latest version of the postcards package installed from CRAN:&#xA;install.packages(&amp;#34;postcards&amp;#34;) Restart your R session. If you use RStudio, use the menu item Session &amp;gt; Restart R or the associated keyboard shortcut:&#xA;Ctrl + Shift + F10 (Windows and Linux) or Command + Shift + F10 (Mac OS). packageVersion(&amp;#34;postcards&amp;#34;) [1] ‘0.2.0’ Create GitHub repo Online.&#xA;Clone GitHub repo usethis::create_from_github(&amp;#34;https://github.com/apreshill/global-postcard.git&amp;#34;) &amp;#x2728; Commit &amp;amp; Push! &amp;#x2728;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using blogdown</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/collection/day02/02-blogdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/collection/day02/02-blogdown/</guid>
      <description>Pre-requisites First, make sure you have the latest version of the blogdown package installed from CRAN:&#xA;install.packages(&amp;#34;blogdoown&amp;#34;) Restart your R session. If you use RStudio, use the menu item Session &amp;gt; Restart R or the associated keyboard shortcut:&#xA;Ctrl + Shift + F10 (Windows and Linux) or Command + Shift + F10 (Mac OS). packageVersion(&amp;#34;blogdown&amp;#34;) [1] ‘1.0’ Create GitHub repo Online.&#xA;Clone GitHub repo usethis::create_from_github(&amp;#34;https://github.com/apreshill/global-blogdown.git&amp;#34;) &amp;#x2728; Commit &amp;amp; Push! &amp;#x2728;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A distill site</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/collection/day01/03-distill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/collection/day01/03-distill/</guid>
      <description>Pre-requisites First, make sure you have the latest version of the distill package installed from CRAN:&#xA;install.packages(&amp;quot;distill&amp;quot;) Restart your R session. If you use RStudio, use the menu item Session &amp;gt; Restart R or the associated keyboard shortcut:&#xA;Ctrl + Shift + F10 (Windows and Linux) or Command + Shift + F10 (Mac OS). packageVersion(&amp;#34;distill&amp;#34;) # [1] ‘1.2’ Create GitHub repo Online.&#xA;Clone GitHub repo usethis::create_from_github(&amp;quot;https://github.com/apreshill/global-distill.git&amp;quot;) &amp;#x2728; Commit &amp;amp; Push!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warm woolen mittens</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/collection/day02/03-blogdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/collection/day02/03-blogdown/</guid>
      <description> Hi, I&#39;m the here-bot cat! Use me to find your way in your website.&#xA;Here I am: content/collection/day02/03-blogdown/index.md To remove me, delete this line inside that file: {{&amp;lt; here &amp;gt;}}&#xA;My content section is: collection My layout is: single-series part 2! does this work? now for some very cool things more get ready! </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Operators for Optimizing Focused Ultrasound Therapy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/research/neural-operators/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/research/neural-operators/</guid>
      <description>A new way to both optimize and personalize spinal cord injury treatment This research focuses on developing a pipeline to enable personalized treatment plans for spinal cord injury. Understanding where to place a focused ultrasound transducer in surgery to optimize therapeutic effect requires computational simulations. Numerical solvers take too long to generate the necessary pressure maps, taking up to 5 hours to provide accurate results. The time and cost-intensive nature of this approach is unfeasible for intraoperative use-cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A novel open-source ultrasound dataset with deep learning benchmarks for spinal cord injury localization and anatomical segmentation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/publications/arxiv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/publications/arxiv/</guid>
      <description>Published in: ArXiv</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computer Vision on Medical Images</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/research/computer-vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/research/computer-vision/</guid>
      <description>Continuous evaluation of clinical metrics necessitates integrated computer vision algorithms to detect relevant features from ultrasound images. My research efforts have centered on developing tools for automating and aiding with diagnostics in spinal cord injury. Using ultrasound and wearable technology, we can monitor patient health continuously with ultrasonic imaging. Rather than the current treatment paradigm, where the spinal cord is imaged for sparse and discrete time points after the injury, we can continuously evaluate the spinal cord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visualizing Tactile Feedback: An Overview of Current Technologies With a Focus on Ultrasound Elastography</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/publications/front-med-tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/publications/front-med-tech/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: Tissue elasticity remains an essential biomarker of health and is indicative of irregularities such as tumors or infection. The timely detection of such abnormalities is crucial for the prevention of disease progression and complications that arise from late-stage illnesses. However, at both the bedside and the operating table, there is a distinct lack of tactile feedback for deep-seated tissue. As surgical techniques advance toward remote or minimally invasive options to reduce infection risk and hasten healing time, surgeons lose the ability to manually palpate tissue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unidirectional brain-computer interface: Artificial neural network encoding natural images to fMRI response in the visual cortex.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/publications/ieee-icassp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/publications/ieee-icassp/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: While significant advancements in artificial intelligence (AI) have catalyzed progress across various domains, its full potential in understanding visual perception remains underexplored. We propose an artificial neural network dubbed VISION, an acronym for “Visual Interface System for Imaging Output of Neural activity,” to mimic the human brain and show how it can foster neuroscientific inquiries. Using visual and contextual inputs, this multimodal model predicts the brain’s functional magnetic resonance imaging (fMRI) scan response to natural images.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying tethered spinal cord tension: Ultrasound elastography results from computational, cadaveric, and intraoperative first-in-human studies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/publications/nat-com-med/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/publications/nat-com-med/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: Background: Tension in the spinal cord is a trademark of tethered cord syndrome. Unfortunately, existing tests cannot quantify tension across the bulk of the cord, making the diagnostic evaluation of stretch ambiguous. A potential non-destructive metric for spinal cord tension is ultrasound-derived shear wave velocity (SWV). The velocity is sensitive to tissue elasticity and boundary conditions including strain. We use the term Ultrasound Tensography to describe the acoustic evaluation of tension with SWV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Patient-specific Preplanning Treatment Algorithm for Focused Ultrasound Therapy of Spinal Cord Injury</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/publications/ieee-ner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/publications/ieee-ner/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: Focused ultrasound (FUS) is an increasingly prevalent therapeutic tool used in medicine to treat patients non-invasively, cost-effectively, and without any ionizing radiation. Depending on the clinical application, therapeutic ultrasound can be used for tissue ablation, physiotherapy, lithotripsy, and drug delivery, among other therapies. For the treatment to be effective, it is important to understand the acoustic pressure profile in the tissue to ensure the focal point intensity is sufficient to achieve therapy without damaging the tissue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computational modeling towards focused ultrasound therapy for spinal cord injury: visualization of beam propagation through patient-specific anatomy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/publications/spie-med-imaging/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/publications/spie-med-imaging/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: Ultrasound holds promise for use in spinal cord injury cases for both diagnostic and therapeutic purposes. Focused ultrasound applications demand an added threshold of study to ensure the safety and efficacy of the therapy. For optimal treatment outcomes, it is crucial to understand whether relevant structures are being targeting with sufficient energy without damaging neighboring tissue and vasculature. However, it is difficult to predict the expected displacement and pressure profile of the ultrasound wavefront due to challenges with visualizing an acoustic beam in real-time and complex patient-specific anatomy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultrasound Simulations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/research/ultrasound-simulations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/research/ultrasound-simulations/</guid>
      <description>Generating acoustic phantoms of patient-specific spinal cords to investigate the theraputic efficacy of focused ultrasound transducer placement Therapeutic focused ultrasound is a rapidly maturing technology, showing promise for alleviating the side effects of spinal cord injury by stimulating blood circulation to promote healing. Focused ultrasound can deliver therapy to sub-millimeter focal regions, allowing clinicians to pinpoint the site of injury while minimizing impact on surrounding tissues. During my PhD, I have been interested in investigating the effects of patient spinal cord geometry on focused ultrasound wave propagation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulated driving in the epilepsy monitoring unit: Effects of seizure type, consciousness, and motor impairment</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/publications/epilepsia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/publications/epilepsia/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: People with epilepsy face serious driving restrictions, determined using retrospective studies. To relate seizure characteristics to driving impairment, we aimed to study driving behavior during seizures with a simulator. Patients in the Yale New Haven Hospital undergoing video-electroencephalographic monitoring used a laptop-based driving simulator during ictal events. Driving function was evaluated by video review and analyzed in relation to seizure type, impairment of consciousness/responsiveness, or motor impairment during seizures. Fifty-one seizures in 30 patients were studied.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Design of the Alpha CubeSat: Technology Demonstration of a ChipSat-Equipped Retroreflective Light Sail</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/publications/aiaa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/publications/aiaa/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: This paper provides an overview of Alpha, a rapidly developed, low-cost CubeSat mission to verify the performance of a highly retroreflective material for light-sail propulsion. Designed, integrated, and tested by students of the Space Systems Design Studio at Cornell University, this mission demonstrates a number of key technologies that enable next-generation capabilities for space exploration. In particular, this paper focuses on the novel application of ChipSats (gram scale spacecraft-on-a-chip technology) as a means of verifying Alpha&amp;rsquo;s sail orbit and attitude dynamics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computational Neuroscience for Understanding Epilepsy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/research/computational-neuroscience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/research/computational-neuroscience/</guid>
      <description>Studying patterns in brain electrical activity can provide insights on when a seizure will occur. During my tenure at Yale School of Medicine (2020-2021) as a computational neuroscience research associate in the Blumenfeld Lab, I developed signal processing pipelines to study and identify indicators of seizure onset. By separating the EEG signals of patients with epilepsy into their frequency subcomponents, I quantified the changes in brain signals before, during, and after a seizure to find patterns that indicate loss of consciousness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Systems Design</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/research/space-system-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/research/space-system-design/</guid>
      <description>Facilitating innovations that dramatically increase the capabilities of the next generation of small spacecraft The mission of the Space Systems Design Studion is pioneering multiple techniques that have the potential to fundamentally change deep space exploration. Highlighted innovations include, but are not limited to: a primarily 3D printed spacecraft structure, the use of a RockBlock modem for decentralized communication, the placement of holograms on the spacecraft, and of course, the first release of a free-flying light sail into Low Earth Orbit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuromorphic Circuits</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/research/neuromorphic-computing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/research/neuromorphic-computing/</guid>
      <description>For my Masters Thesis at Cornell University (2019-2020), I worked on developing a computational system to emulate the mammalian olfactory system using chemosensors, microcontrollers, and a machine learning classification algorithm. The goal for this system is to learn and classify new odors rapidly and robustly despite interference from other smells, much like our own olfactory system. More information on my thesis can be found in the link above!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 13:38:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/contact/</guid>
      <description>** Contact page don&amp;rsquo;t contain a body, just the front matter above. See form.html in the layouts folder.&#xA;Formspree requires a (free) account and new form to be set up. The link is made on the final published url in the field: Restrict to Domain. It is possible to register up to 2 emails free and you can select which one you want the forms to go to within Formspree in the Settings tab.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contributors</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/contributors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/contributors/</guid>
      <description>Thank you to all the folks who have contributed both technical and creative skills to this project:&#xA;Desirée De Leon &amp;#x1f992; (designed 5 of the custom color themes, made illustrations for the workshop, and provided general aesthetic feedback along the way)&#xA;Garrick Aden-Buie &amp;#x1f9d9; (debugged headroom.js and lent his panelset.js code to the theme)&#xA;Allison Horst &amp;#x1f415; (awesome illustrations of campfires, seedlings, and evergreens, as well as my R Markdown hedgehog mascot &amp;#x1f994;)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/cv/</guid>
      <description> Click here for a PDF of my CV! </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/license/</guid>
      <description>My blog posts are released under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Course Instructor Modeling, Simulations, and Artificial Intelligence for Optimizing Neurosurgery Designed and instructed course for Johns Hopkins undergraduate students&#xA;Fall 2024&#xA;Biomedical Engineering Innovation Summer 2024 and Fall 2024&#xA;Teaching Assistant Principles of Design of Biomedical Instrumentation Graduate teaching assistant at Johns Hopkins University&#xA;Fall 2022&#xA;Computer Networks and Telecommunications Graduate teaching assistant at Cornell University&#xA;Spring 2020&#xA;Intelligent Physical Systems undergraduate teaching assistant at Cornell University&#xA;Fall 2019</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
