<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Avisha Kumar</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4321/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Avisha Kumar</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4321/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Netlify</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/collection/day02/01-netlify/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/collection/day02/01-netlify/</guid>
      <description>So far, we&amp;rsquo;ve been leveraging GitHub Pages for publishing. This works great, but for blogdown we&amp;rsquo;ll start using Netlify. Let&amp;rsquo;s start RIGHT NOW with a site we&amp;rsquo;ve already built and published.&#xA;Pre-requisites Pick either your postcards site, or your distill site from day 01. Refresh your memory- which repository was it again?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A first post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/blog/spoonful-series/01-spoonful/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/blog/spoonful-series/01-spoonful/</guid>
      <description> Hi, I&#39;m the here-bot cat! Use me to find your way in your website.&#xA;Here I am: content/blog/spoonful-series/01-spoonful.md To remove me, delete this line inside that file: {{&amp;lt; here &amp;gt;}}&#xA;My content section is: blog My layout is: single-series does this work? or this? Let&amp;rsquo;s start.&#xA;beginning middle end </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A GitHub profile</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/collection/day01/01-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/collection/day01/01-github/</guid>
      <description>Profile https://docs.github.com/en/github/setting-up-and-managing-your-github-profile/personalizing-your-profile&#xA;Pin projects to profile https://docs.github.com/en/github/setting-up-and-managing-your-github-profile/pinning-items-to-your-profile&#xA;Profile README This is new! Let&amp;rsquo;s do it:&#xA;https://docs.github.com/en/github/setting-up-and-managing-your-github-profile/managing-your-profile-readme</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prework</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/collection/prework/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/collection/prework/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Introducing Yourself Online workshop! We look forward to meeting you. Before attending the workshop, please complete the following prework.&#xA;Set up RStudio Cloud Sign up for a free RStudio Cloud account at https://rstudio.cloud/ before the workshop. I recommend logging in with an existing Google or GitHub account, if you have one (rather than creating a new account with another password you have to remember). I want you to be able to work from your own laptop in this workshop, but Cloud is an important back-up plan should you run into troubles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A postcard</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/collection/day01/02-postcards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/collection/day01/02-postcards/</guid>
      <description>Pre-requisites First, make sure you have the latest version of the postcards package installed from CRAN:&#xA;install.packages(&amp;#34;postcards&amp;#34;) Restart your R session. If you use RStudio, use the menu item Session &amp;gt; Restart R or the associated keyboard shortcut:&#xA;Ctrl + Shift + F10 (Windows and Linux) or Command + Shift + F10 (Mac OS). packageVersion(&amp;#34;postcards&amp;#34;) [1] ‘0.2.0’ Create GitHub repo Online.&#xA;Clone GitHub repo usethis::create_from_github(&amp;#34;https://github.com/apreshill/global-postcard.git&amp;#34;) &amp;#x2728; Commit &amp;amp; Push! &amp;#x2728;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A second post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/blog/spoonful-series/02-spoonful/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/blog/spoonful-series/02-spoonful/</guid>
      <description> Hi, I&#39;m the here-bot cat! Use me to find your way in your website.&#xA;Here I am: content/blog/spoonful-series/02-spoonful/index.md To remove me, delete this line inside that file: {{&amp;lt; here &amp;gt;}}&#xA;My content section is: blog My layout is: single-series Images in this page bundle: /blog/spoonful-series/02-spoonful/sidebar-inverse.jpg part 2! does this work? now for some very cool things more get ready! </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using blogdown</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/collection/day02/02-blogdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/collection/day02/02-blogdown/</guid>
      <description>Pre-requisites First, make sure you have the latest version of the blogdown package installed from CRAN:&#xA;install.packages(&amp;#34;blogdoown&amp;#34;) Restart your R session. If you use RStudio, use the menu item Session &amp;gt; Restart R or the associated keyboard shortcut:&#xA;Ctrl + Shift + F10 (Windows and Linux) or Command + Shift + F10 (Mac OS). packageVersion(&amp;#34;blogdown&amp;#34;) [1] ‘1.0’ Create GitHub repo Online.&#xA;Clone GitHub repo usethis::create_from_github(&amp;#34;https://github.com/apreshill/global-blogdown.git&amp;#34;) &amp;#x2728; Commit &amp;amp; Push! &amp;#x2728;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A third post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/blog/spoonful-series/03-spoonful/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/blog/spoonful-series/03-spoonful/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&#39;m the here-bot cat! Use me to find your way in your website.&#xA;Here I am: content/blog/spoonful-series/03-spoonful/index.markdown Here is my R Markdown source file: blog/spoonful-series/03-spoonful/index.Rmarkdown You&#39;ll want to edit this file, then re-knit to see the changes take effect in your site preview.&#xA;To remove me, delete this line inside that file: {{&amp;lt; here &amp;gt;}}&#xA;My content section is: blog My layout is: single-series Images in this page bundle: /blog/spoonful-series/03-spoonful/featured-photo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A distill site</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/collection/day01/03-distill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/collection/day01/03-distill/</guid>
      <description>Pre-requisites First, make sure you have the latest version of the distill package installed from CRAN:&#xA;install.packages(&amp;quot;distill&amp;quot;) Restart your R session. If you use RStudio, use the menu item Session &amp;gt; Restart R or the associated keyboard shortcut:&#xA;Ctrl + Shift + F10 (Windows and Linux) or Command + Shift + F10 (Mac OS). packageVersion(&amp;#34;distill&amp;#34;) # [1] ‘1.2’ Create GitHub repo Online.&#xA;Clone GitHub repo usethis::create_from_github(&amp;quot;https://github.com/apreshill/global-distill.git&amp;quot;) &amp;#x2728; Commit &amp;amp; Push!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warm woolen mittens</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/collection/day02/03-blogdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/collection/day02/03-blogdown/</guid>
      <description> Hi, I&#39;m the here-bot cat! Use me to find your way in your website.&#xA;Here I am: content/collection/day02/03-blogdown/index.md To remove me, delete this line inside that file: {{&amp;lt; here &amp;gt;}}&#xA;My content section is: collection My layout is: single-series part 2! does this work? now for some very cool things more get ready! </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visualizing Tactile Feedback: An Overview of Current Technologies With a Focus on Ultrasound Elastography</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/talk/front-med-tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/talk/front-med-tech/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: Tissue elasticity remains an essential biomarker of health and is indicative of irregularities such as tumors or infection. The timely detection of such abnormalities is crucial for the prevention of disease progression and complications that arise from late-stage illnesses. However, at both the bedside and the operating table, there is a distinct lack of tactile feedback for deep-seated tissue. As surgical techniques advance toward remote or minimally invasive options to reduce infection risk and hasten healing time, surgeons lose the ability to manually palpate tissue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unidirectional brain-computer interface: Artificial neural network encoding natural images to fMRI response in the visual cortex.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/talk/ieee-icassp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/talk/ieee-icassp/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: While significant advancements in artificial intelligence (AI) have catalyzed progress across various domains, its full potential in understanding visual perception remains underexplored. We propose an artificial neural network dubbed VISION, an acronym for “Visual Interface System for Imaging Output of Neural activity,” to mimic the human brain and show how it can foster neuroscientific inquiries. Using visual and contextual inputs, this multimodal model predicts the brain’s functional magnetic resonance imaging (fMRI) scan response to natural images.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying tethered spinal cord tension: Ultrasound elastography results from computational, cadaveric, and intraoperative first-in-human studies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/talk/nat-com-med/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/talk/nat-com-med/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: Background: Tension in the spinal cord is a trademark of tethered cord syndrome. Unfortunately, existing tests cannot quantify tension across the bulk of the cord, making the diagnostic evaluation of stretch ambiguous. A potential non-destructive metric for spinal cord tension is ultrasound-derived shear wave velocity (SWV). The velocity is sensitive to tissue elasticity and boundary conditions including strain. We use the term Ultrasound Tensography to describe the acoustic evaluation of tension with SWV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Patient-specific Preplanning Treatment Algorithm for Focused Ultrasound Therapy of Spinal Cord Injury</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/talk/ieee-ner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/talk/ieee-ner/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: Focused ultrasound (FUS) is an increasingly prevalent therapeutic tool used in medicine to treat patients non-invasively, cost-effectively, and without any ionizing radiation. Depending on the clinical application, therapeutic ultrasound can be used for tissue ablation, physiotherapy, lithotripsy, and drug delivery, among other therapies. For the treatment to be effective, it is important to understand the acoustic pressure profile in the tissue to ensure the focal point intensity is sufficient to achieve therapy without damaging the tissue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computational modeling towards focused ultrasound therapy for spinal cord injury: visualization of beam propagation through patient-specific anatomy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/talk/spie-med-imaging/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/talk/spie-med-imaging/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: Ultrasound holds promise for use in spinal cord injury cases for both diagnostic and therapeutic purposes. Focused ultrasound applications demand an added threshold of study to ensure the safety and efficacy of the therapy. For optimal treatment outcomes, it is crucial to understand whether relevant structures are being targeting with sufficient energy without damaging neighboring tissue and vasculature. However, it is difficult to predict the expected displacement and pressure profile of the ultrasound wavefront due to challenges with visualizing an acoustic beam in real-time and complex patient-specific anatomy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulated driving in the epilepsy monitoring unit: Effects of seizure type, consciousness, and motor impairment</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/talk/epilepsia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/talk/epilepsia/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: People with epilepsy face serious driving restrictions, determined using retrospective studies. To relate seizure characteristics to driving impairment, we aimed to study driving behavior during seizures with a simulator. Patients in the Yale New Haven Hospital undergoing video-electroencephalographic monitoring used a laptop-based driving simulator during ictal events. Driving function was evaluated by video review and analyzed in relation to seizure type, impairment of consciousness/responsiveness, or motor impairment during seizures. Fifty-one seizures in 30 patients were studied.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up your social</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/blog/social/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/blog/social/</guid>
      <description>There are five places where you can choose to show social icons. Here is the tl;dr:&#xA;site header (set in config.toml), site footer (set in config.toml), homepage (set in content/_index.md), about page in the sidebar (set in content/about/sidebar/index.md), and contact page (set in content/form/contact.md). Read on to learn how to set up your social icons, and how to show/hide them.&#xA;Configure social Wherever you end up wanting to show your social icons, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to start by setting up the links in your site config.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Style your site colors</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/blog/color-themes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/blog/color-themes/</guid>
      <description>You can totally customize your site&amp;rsquo;s theme colors within minutes of creating a new site. Read on to find out how, and decide which of the three options meets your needs.&#xA;Use a color theme Hugo Apéro includes 8 built-in color themes that work &amp;ldquo;out of the box.&amp;rdquo; This means you can use a color theme to quickly customize the look of your site without needing to write any CSS. You can select the color theme in your config.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Style your site typography</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/blog/fonts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/blog/fonts/</guid>
      <description>As with color themes, you can completely customize your site&amp;rsquo;s fonts within minutes of creating a new site. How you do it depends on how much control and customization you need.&#xA;Embedded fonts Hugo Apéro includes 6 embedded fonts that work &amp;ldquo;out of the box.&amp;rdquo; We selected 3 serif and 3 sans-serif options that we thought looked good with this theme, in our humble opinions. All embedded fonts include real italics so you may emphasize to your heart&amp;rsquo;s content &amp;#x2764;&amp;#xfe0f;!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An evergreen post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/blog/evergreen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/blog/evergreen/</guid>
      <description>Rendering mathematical equations Examples from the mathjax demo. But they work with katex as well.&#xA;Rmarkdown In .Rmarkdown documents, you can use either&#xA;$a \ne 0$ to get inline math: \(a \ne 0\). There is no conflict with using dollar symbols regularly, because knitr automatically escapes freestanding dollar symbols.&#xA;And you can use&#xA;$x = {-b \pm \sqrt{b^2-4ac} \over 2a}.$$ to get a math paragraph:&#xA;$$x = {-b \pm \sqrt{b^2-4ac} \over 2a}.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Design of the Alpha CubeSat: Technology Demonstration of a ChipSat-Equipped Retroreflective Light Sail</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/talk/aiaa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/talk/aiaa/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: This paper provides an overview of Alpha, a rapidly developed, low-cost CubeSat mission to verify the performance of a highly retroreflective material for light-sail propulsion. Designed, integrated, and tested by students of the Space Systems Design Studio at Cornell University, this mission demonstrates a number of key technologies that enable next-generation capabilities for space exploration. In particular, this paper focuses on the novel application of ChipSats (gram scale spacecraft-on-a-chip technology) as a means of verifying Alpha&amp;rsquo;s sail orbit and attitude dynamics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using panelsets</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/blog/seedling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/blog/seedling/</guid>
      <description>Courtesy of panelset.js by Garrick Aden-Buie, from his xaringanExtra package: https://pkg.garrickadenbuie.com/xaringanExtra/#/panelset&#xA;For example, this panelset:&#xA;Hello! &amp;#x1f44b; hello&#xA;Goodbye &amp;#x1f4a8; goodbye&#xA;Was created by combining this theme&amp;rsquo;s panelset and panel shortcodes:&#xA;{{&amp;lt; panelset class=&amp;#34;greetings&amp;#34; &amp;gt;}} {{&amp;lt; panel name=&amp;#34;Hello! :wave:&amp;#34; &amp;gt;}} hello {{&amp;lt; /panel &amp;gt;}} {{&amp;lt; panel name=&amp;#34;Goodbye :dash:&amp;#34; &amp;gt;}} goodbye {{&amp;lt; /panel &amp;gt;}} {{&amp;lt; /panelset &amp;gt;}} You could also revert to HTML as well. For example, this panelset:&#xA;Question Which came first: the :chicken: or the :egg:?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Rmarkdown post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/blog/rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/blog/rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description> Air quality with(airquality, boxplot(Temp ~ Month)) with(airquality, plot(Ozone ~ Temp)) mlev &amp;lt;- levels(with(airquality, as.factor(Month))) with(airquality, plot(Ozone ~ Temp, pch = as.numeric(mlev), col = mlev)) </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tachyons for Style</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/project/giraffes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/project/giraffes/</guid>
      <description>Tachyons is a design system that allows you to design gorgeous interfaces in the browser with little effort. Because Speed Building this static site generator theme was the first time I used an Atomic (or Functional) CSS system like Tachyons. It&amp;rsquo;s a design system that provides very small (which means fast) CSS modules that you can use in your HTML. So, rather than writing every line of CSS, you apply the style you need as you write your HTML with easy to understand shorthand class names.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSS Grid Scaffold</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/blog/css-grid-scaffold/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/blog/css-grid-scaffold/</guid>
      <description>“Grid is the very first CSS module created specifically to solve the layout problems we&amp;rsquo;ve all been hacking our way around for as long as we&amp;rsquo;ve been making websites.” — Chris House, A Complete Guide to CSS Grid Layout 1&#xA;Overview Since I began building websites in Y2K, I&amp;rsquo;ve lost count how many times the phrase &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;there&amp;rsquo;s got to be a better way to do this&amp;rdquo; has passed my lips.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palmer Penguins</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/project/penguins/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/project/penguins/</guid>
      <description>“Grid is the very first CSS module created specifically to solve the layout problems we&amp;rsquo;ve all been hacking our way around for as long as we&amp;rsquo;ve been making websites.” — Chris House, A Complete Guide to CSS Grid Layout 1&#xA;Since I began building websites in Y2K, I&amp;rsquo;ve lost count how many times the phrase &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;there&amp;rsquo;s got to be a better way to do this&amp;rdquo; has passed my lips. Most times, while fighting with floats and widths of content and sidebars or just basically trying to get something beside something else without using a stupid TABLE.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bakeoff</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/project/bakeoff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/project/bakeoff/</guid>
      <description>Formspree makes it easy to receive submissions from HTML forms on your static website. Functional Form This theme has a form-to-email feature built in, thanks to the simple Formspree integration. All you need to activate the form is a valid recipient email address saved in the front matter of the form (/content/forms/contact.md). Of course, the example shown below (your@email.here) must not be used. Please use your actual email address.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Built-in Contact Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/blog/built-in-contact-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/blog/built-in-contact-form/</guid>
      <description>Formspree makes it easy to receive submissions from HTML forms on your static website. Functional Form This theme has a form-to-email feature built in, thanks to the simple Formspree integration. All you need to activate the form is a valid recipient email address saved in the front matter of the form (/content/forms/contact.md). Of course, the example shown below (your@email.here) must not be used. Please use your actual email address.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 13:38:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/contact/</guid>
      <description>** Contact page don&amp;rsquo;t contain a body, just the front matter above. See form.html in the layouts folder.&#xA;Formspree requires a (free) account and new form to be set up. The link is made on the final published url in the field: Restrict to Domain. It is possible to register up to 2 emails free and you can select which one you want the forms to go to within Formspree in the Settings tab.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Typography Styles &amp; Element Examples</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/elements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 12:27:33 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/elements/</guid>
      <description>Font Sizes A A A A A A A A 6rem&#xA;(96px) 5rem&#xA;(80px) 3rem&#xA;(48px) 2.25rem&#xA;(36px) 1.5rem&#xA;(24px) 1.25rem&#xA;(20px) 1rem&#xA;(16px) .875rem&#xA;(14px) Type Samples Head&amp;shy;line Sub&amp;shy;head&amp;shy;line Level 1 Heading One page to rule them all...well, not really. This page displays sample typography and page elements to illustrate their style. Things like headings and paragraphs showing the beautiful type scale, form elements, tabular data, and image layouts just to name a few.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contributors</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/contributors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/contributors/</guid>
      <description>Thank you to all the folks who have contributed both technical and creative skills to this project:&#xA;Desirée De Leon &amp;#x1f992; (designed 5 of the custom color themes, made illustrations for the workshop, and provided general aesthetic feedback along the way)&#xA;Garrick Aden-Buie &amp;#x1f9d9; (debugged headroom.js and lent his panelset.js code to the theme)&#xA;Allison Horst &amp;#x1f415; (awesome illustrations of campfires, seedlings, and evergreens, as well as my R Markdown hedgehog mascot &amp;#x1f994;)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/license/</guid>
      <description>My blog posts are released under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
